export const emojis = [
  { question: '🤐💃', answer: 'shut up and dance' },
  { question: '👨🔛🌙', answer: 'man on the moon' },
  { question: '☔️🐱🐶', answer: 'raining cats and dogs' },
  { question: '🥊🍺❤️', answer: 'punch drunk love' },
  { question: '🚫😭⤴️⤵️💦🥛', answer: 'dont cry over spilled milk' },
  { question: '🙏💩', answer: 'holy crap' },
  { question: '👀🐯', answer: 'eye of the tiger' },
  { question: '🐝🐝↔️🚫🐝🐝➡️❓', answer: 'to be or not to be that is the question' },
  { question: '🚫☠️🔪➡️💪', answer: 'what doesnt kill you makes you stronger' },
  { question: '🚫🤡🔁', answer: 'stop clowning around' },
  { question: '🐦✋🐦🐦🌳', answer: 'a bird in the hand is worth two in the bush' }
]

